# MIKL WOLFE

510-501-5032 | wolfe@mikl.io github.com/chiefmikey | linkedin.com/in/miklwolfe

### **PROFILE**

Software engineer experienced in a large variety of full-stack languages and frameworks. Strong comprehension of advanced technologies and systems including DevOps. Extensive experience developing high-level implementations autonomously. Career began in UX/UI design and progressed into software engineering.

### RECENT EXPERIENCE

Marketron | Full-Stack Software Engineer | March 2022 - October 2023

Skills: Technical Leadership, Technical Design, Mentoring, PostgreSQL, Cypress, DevOps, GitHub Actions CI/CD

- Drove new product features including technical design documentation and execution strategy
- Supported integrations across teams including QA and DevOps and mentored junior developers
- Substitute for engineering manager in client issues, deployments, sprint planning, etc.

Marketron | Junior Software Engineer | January 2022 - March 2022

Skills: Node, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Express, Jest, HTML5, SCSS, Git, Postman, Microservices

- Collaborated closely with offshore resources across multiple front and back-end microservices
- Debugged and resolved time-sensitive client issues and prepared hotfixes for deployment
- Demonstrated key concepts after completing a shift-left developer driven testing seminar series

Independent Contract | Full-Stack Software Engineer | April 2021 - December 2021

Skills: Node, TypeScript, React, Axios, Koa, MongoDB, Docker, AWS, Load/Stress Testing, Shell Scripting, Linux

- Increased load capacity of a site with heavy traffic for a startup in the cryptocurrency industry
- Migrated an inefficient site to a scalable React platform for a growing beverage company

## PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

Innovation Roundtable | UX/UI Designer | January 2019 – January 2021

Skills: Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, HTML5, CSS, Google Analytics, Mailchimp

- Strengthened user experience with refined web design and front-end optimizations
- Developed new platform features and content offered as resources to customers
- Highlighted performance and engagement with custom SEO and analytics reports

The Simon Collective | UX/UI Designer | March 2017 – January 2019

Skills: Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, HTML5, CSS, Cloudflare

- Designed and implemented a web portfolio site to carefully represent the brand message
- Managed and maintained technical needs including domain DNS and hosting
- Refreshed branding and created clearly presented guidelines for future consistency

#### **EDUCATION**

Hack Reactor Galvanize | Advanced Software Engineering Immersive | 2020 - 2021

SAE Expression College | BAS, Motion Graphic Design | 2009 – 2012

Berklee College of Music | Music Production | 2008